{
    "id": "cf3516557220497c8240442042a5ddd7",
    "title": "Simple, Complex Vs. Compound",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Owing to his illness, he could not attend the meeting.",
            "description": "A simple sentence has just one finite verb.",
            "answers": [
                "Simple sentence",
                "Complex sentence",
                "Compound sentence"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The doctor said that I had to quit smoking.",
            "description": "A complex sentence has one main clause and one or more subordinate clauses.",
            "answers": [
                "Simple sentence",
                "Complex sentence",
                "Compound sentence"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "That carpet needs to be cleaned.",
            "description": "A simple sentence has just one finite verb.",
            "answers": [
                "Simple sentence",
                "Complex sentence",
                "Compound sentence"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Will you miss me when I am away?",
            "description": "A complex sentence has one main clause and one or more subordinate clauses.",
            "answers": [
                "Simple sentence",
                "Complex sentence",
                "Compound sentence"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I miss living in the mountains.",
            "description": "A simple sentence has just one finite verb.",
            "answers": [
                "Simple sentence",
                "Complex sentence",
                "Compound sentence"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The missing girl was found at her auntâ€™s place.",
            "description": "A simple sentence has just one finite verb.",
            "answers": [
                "Simple sentence",
                "Complex sentence",
                "Compound sentence"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "How they reached there is unknown.",
            "description": "A complex sentence has one main clause and one or more subordinate clauses.",
            "answers": [
                "Simple sentence",
                "Complex sentence",
                "Compound sentence"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She opened the book and started making notes.",
            "description": "A compound sentence has two or more independent clauses of the same rank.",
            "answers": [
                "Simple",
                "Complex",
                "Compound"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He is neither intelligent nor efficient.",
            "description": "A compound sentence has two or more independent clauses of the same rank.",
            "answers": [
                "Simple",
                "Complex",
                "Compound"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The man told me to go away.",
            "description": "A simple sentence has just one finite verb.",
            "answers": [
                "Simple",
                "Complex",
                "Compound"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He stopped to say Hi.",
            "description": "A simple sentence has just one finite verb.",
            "answers": [
                "Simple",
                "Complex",
                "Compound"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I must be losing weight.",
            "description": "A simple sentence has just one finite verb.",
            "answers": [
                "Simple",
                "Complex",
                "Compound"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}